Privacy Policy
==============

[Home](https://epubor.com/) > [About](https://epubor.com/about.html) >[Privacy Policy](https://www.epubor.com/privacy-policy.html)

Support Center

Privacy Policy
--------------

Epubor Software is committed to protecting client's privacy. We will only collect your basic information for better CRM and after-sale service. We do not distribute or share your personal information with any individual or organization. Epubor will never sell your personal information in any situation.

### Update: Epubor will be GDPR compliant by May 25th

Epubor has updated its Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, effective May 25, 2018. These changes were made primarily in preparation for the EU’s new data privacy law, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Our customers' right to privacy is a main priority for Epubor team and because of this, Epubor team reaffirms its commitment to safeguarding the personal data of our customers, subscribers, and anyone who visits our websites.

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your Personal Information, then [please open a ticket](https://share.hsforms.com/1XMDdDw_CReqsb5-qCwX6fgc1yk8).

### What information do we collect? What do we use it for?

When you leave a message on our website by commenting, your full name and email address will be required. This information is used to help us answer visitor's question and send a notification email to the commentor.

When you place an order on our website, you will be jumped to third-party online payment service webiste like Paypal. The payment website will collect your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. The credit card information is only used for transaction and the payment website will not transfer your credit card information to us.

For the rest, we will collect your full name, email address, the product your purchased, and the country information. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

### How do the 3rd party payment websites protect customer's credit card information?

Epubor uses secure server hosted by RegNow, 2checkout, Stripe and Paypal, they encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, your credit card information is only used for online transition.

### 2checkout, Stripe and Paypal

Founded in 2006, 2checkout(Avangate) is headquartered in Amsterdam, The Netherlands. We are the agile eCommerce solutions provider trusted by Software and SaaS companies to grow their eCommerce business worldwide through any channel, any model.

PayPal is the faster, safer way to pay and get paid online, via a mobile device and in store. The service gives people simpler ways to send money without sharing financial information, and with the flexibility to pay using their account balances, bank accounts, credit cards or promotional financing.

Stripe offers payment methods such as bank transfers, bank redirects, buy now, pay later, cards, real-time payments, wallets, and cash-based vouchers.

### Cookie policy

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). But please be aware that if block cookies in your browser settings, you may not have full access to all the web pages, and it may lead a failure to your transaction.

3  [(0 reviews)](https://epubor.com/privacy-policy-sms.htm)

* HOT products

* SUPPORT

* CONNECT WITH US

* Subscribe
*  Submit

Copyright © 2011-2024 www.epubor.com. All rights reserved.
